Guide to the Hunter Ripley Rawlings papers, 1995-2006.
Rawlings, Hunter Ripley papers, 1995-2006
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Hunter Ripley Rawlings papers, 1995-2006.
3-13-2843
Hunter R. Rawlings
130.4 cubic ft., 987 megabytes.
Correspondence, Manuscripts, Publications, Reports
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, subject files, administrative working papers, and other records of the President of Cornell University.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Born in Norfolk, Virginia, Hunter R. Rawlings III was a 1966 graduate of Haverford College, with honors in classics, and received his Ph.D. degree from Princeton University in 1970. His scholarly publications include a book, The Structure of Thucydides’ History (Princeton University Press, 1981). After serving as president of the University of Iowa from 1988 to 1995, Rawlings began his appointment as Cornell University’s president. A national spokesperson for higher education, he has served as chair of the Ivy Council of Presidents and of the Association of American Universities, and was a member of the American Council on Education board. He is a member of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences and serves on the board of managers of his alma mater, Haverford College, and on the National Advisory Committee of the Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation. He also serves on the boards of the National Humanities Center and the American School of Classical Studies at Athens.
At the conclusion of his presidency in 2003, Rawlings was elected president emeritus and began serving as a full-time professor in Cornell’s Departments of Classics and History. He was then was appointed by the Board of Trustees to serve as interim president of Cornell after Jeffrey Lehman resigned as the university’s president. In 2016, he once again took on the role of interim president upon the death of President Elizabeth Garrett.
See the Cornell Office of the President website for more information about the Presidency of Hunter R. Rawlings III.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, subject files, administrative working papers, and other records of the President of Cornell University.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Rawlings, Hunter R.; Cornell University--Presidents.; Cornell University--Administration.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to the permission of the office of origin. Consult the University Archivist. Restriction reviews may take up to a month for completion.
Arrangement: collection consists of routine administration records.
Not all the items in the collection are covered by this guide.
Link to the printed finding aid for Boxes 1-102. PDF file
The Cornell University Archives Web Archive has a collection copies of speeches and essays given by President Rawlings here: https://wayback.archive-it.org/2566/20140616012613/http://cornell-classic.univcomm.cornell.edu/president/10_rawlings/speeches.cfm#
SERIES LIST
Series I. Guide to boxes 1-102
Series II. Papers
Boxes 94; 103-104; 107-128
Series III. Interim President Papers (June 2005-July 2006)
Speeches
Box 130, 131
Series IV. Audio and Video
Boxes 105-106
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Guide to boxes 1-102
  - Box list is available by clicking here. PDF file.
- Series II. Papers
  - Christmas shows, 1980-1989 (Box 94)
  - BioSci331 Class Videos, Jerry Feigenstein & Matt Slaybaugh, 1995 (Box 94)
  - Seminar-on-wheels: Extension tour, August 29, 1995 (Box 94)
  - Second Tuesday, September 1995 (Box 94)
  - Second Tuesday, November 14, 1995 (Box 94)
  - Second Tuesday, May 14, 1996 (Box 94)
  - Cornell Medical College: celebrating 100 years, 1898-1998 (Box 94)
  - Cornell Commencement 5/24/1998 (Box 94)
  - New York-Cornell: brilliant care 19-- (Box 94)
  - Cornell '59: Class on the cutting edge (2 copies) 19-- (Box 94)
  - Cornell-Penn Football preview 19-- (Box 94)
  - Task Force Report: Division of Biological Sciences Structural Review I-II, March 18, 1988 (Box 103, Folder 1-2)
  - Jackson Hole, Distance Learning I-III, July 23-24, 1999 (Box 103, Folder 3-5)
  - Professorships Endowed- Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Professorships Endowed- Miscellaneous, 1990-1992 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Professorships Endowed- Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Professorships Endowed- Miscellaneous, 19-- (Box 107, Folder 4-5)
  - Professorships Endowed- Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Proposed Professorships- Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Professorships-A, 1977, 1980, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Professorships-A, 1972, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Professorships-B, 1978-1979, 1981, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Professorships-B, 1968, 1978, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Professorships-B, 1976, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Professorships-C, 1973, 1983, 1985, 1988, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Professorships-C, 1956, 1973, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Professorships-C, 1956, 1979, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Professorship Carpenter, 1987-1991 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Professorship Carpenter, 1968-1988 (Box 107, Folder 17)
    1968-1969, 1972, 1980, 1987-1988
  - Professorship Carpenter, 1967, 1973, 1976, 1986-1987 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - Professorship Carpenter, 1979, 1982, 1986-1987 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Professorship Carpenter, 1969-1982 (Box 107, Folder 20)
    1969-1970, 1978-1979, 1981-1982
  - Professorship- Edmund Ezra Day, 2001 (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - Einaudi Professorship in International Studies, 1988-1992 (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - Einaudi Professorship in International Studies, 1986-1988 (Box 107, Folder 23)
  - Einaudi Professorship in International Studies, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 24)
  - Professorship-Einstein, 1987, 1989-1991 (Box 107, Folder 25)
  - Professorship-Einstein, 1989, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 26)
  - Professorship-Einstein, 1985, 1987, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 27)
  - Professorship-Einstein, 1980-1985 (Box 107, Folder 28)
  - Professorship-Einstein, 1979-1981 (Box 107, Folder 29)
  - Einstein Chair, 1986-1987 (Box 107, Folder 30)
  - Einstein Chair, 1976, 1978, 1985, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 31)
  - Professor Emerson Electric (JGSM), 1979, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 32)
  - Professorships-F, 1970, 1972, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 33)
  - Professorships Ford Foundation Chairs for CIS, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 34)
  - Professorships Ford Foundation- Engineering, 1964-1965, 1973, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 35)
  - Professorships Ford Foundation-Engineering, 1964 (Box 107, Folder 36)
  - Professorships-D, 1988-1989 (Box 107, Folder 37)
  - Professorships-G, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 38)
  - Professorships - Goldwin Smith, 1969-1971, 1974-1976, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 39)
  - Professorships-H-I, 1973, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 40)
  - Professorship-J, 1973, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 41)
  - Professorships-K, 1980, 1986, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 42)
  - Professorships-K, 1990, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 43)
  - Professorships-L, 1992, 1996, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 44)
  - Professorships-L, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 45)
  - Professorships-L, 1980, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 46)
  - Luce Professorship of History and the Arts, 1978, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 47)
  - Luce Professorship-Social Implications of Biotechnology, 1984-1985 (Box 107, Folder 48)
  - Professorships Luce, 1978, 1982, 1984, 1986, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 49)
  - Professorships Luce, 1969, 1973, 1979-1982 (Box 107, Folder 50)
  - Professorships Luce, 1969, 1973-1978 (Box 107, Folder 51)
  - Luce Professorship Proposal, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 52)
  - Professorships-M, 1968, 1989, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 53)
  - Professorships-M, 1978, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 54)
  - Professorships-N, 1973-1976, 1978, 1981, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 55)
  - Professorships-N, 1978-1979 (Box 107, Folder 56)
  - Professorships-N, 1968, 1977, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 57)
  - Professorships-O, 1968, 1977, 1979-1980 (Box 107, Folder 58)
  - Professorships-P, 1965-1993 (Box 107, Folder 59)
    1965, 1967-1968, 1977, 1992-1993
  - Perkins Prize, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 60)
  - Professorships-R, 1980, 1990, 1992-1995 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Professorships-R, 1964-1965, 1973, 1981 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Professorships-S, 1956-1998 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    1956, 1962, 1966, 1968-1969, 1980, 1986, 1990, 1998
  - Professorships-Jacob Gould Schurman, 1976, 1981, 1994-1997 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Professorships-Jacob Gould Schurman, 1968, 1976, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Professorships-Jacob Gould Schurman, 1973-1974, 1976, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Professorships-Richard Schwartz, 1976-1979, 1982-1983 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Professorships-Richard Schwartz, 1970, 1974-1976 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Professorships-Richard Schwartz, 1968-1969, 1971-1974 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Professorship Schweitzer, 1978-1990 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    1978-1979, 1983-1984, 1988, 1990
  - Professorship Schweitzer, 1976, 1978, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Professorship Schweitzer, 1966, 1973-1974, 1976 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Professorships-Senior, John L., 1980-1981, 1985-1986 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Professorships-Senior, John L., 1987-1990, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Professorships-Senior, John L., 1987-1989 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Professorships-Senior, John L., 1986-1987 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - Professorships-T, 1964-1984 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    1964, 1966, 1971, 1973, 1984
  - Professorships-U, 1977, 1986, 1990 (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - Professorship-Maxwell P. Upson, 1964-1972 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    1964, 1966, 1969-1970, 1972
  - Professorships-W, 1973-1988 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    1973-1975, 1978-1981, 1983, 1988
  - Professorships-W, 1959-1987 (Box 108, Folder 21)
    1959, 1964, 1969-1970, 1972-1973, 1980, 1987
  - Professorships-W, 1972 (Box 108, Folder 22)
  - Association of American Universities, 2000-2001 (Box 108, Folder 23-27)
  - Association of American Universities, 1999-2000 (Box 108, Folder 28-34)
  - Association of American Universities - NASULGC Task Force on Accreditation, 1999-2000 (Box 108, Folder 35)
  - Association of American Universities Diversity Statement, 1997 (Box 108, Folder 36)
  - NEH Letter to Congress From Association of American Universities Members, 1997 (Box 108, Folder 37)
  - American Council on Education (ACE), 2000-2001 (Box 108, Folder 38-39)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 2000-2001 (Box 108, Folder 40)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 41)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1979, 1999-2000 (Box 108, Folder 42)
  - Business- Higher Education Forum, 2000-2001 (Box 108, Folder 43-44)
  - Business- Higher Education Forum, 1996, 2000-2001 (Box 108, Folder 45)
  - Campus Compact, 2000-2001 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - N.Y. Campus Compact, 1999-2000 (Box 109, Folder 2-3)
  - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 2000-2001 (Box 109, Folder 4-6)
  - The College Board, 2001 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 2001 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1999-2000 (Box 109, Folder 9-10)
  - 568 Files, 2000-2001 (Box 109, Folder 11-15)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1999-2000 (Box 109, Folder 16-22)
  - Consortium of Social Science Associations, 2000-2001 (Box 109, Folder 23)
  - Council of Competitiveness, 2000-2001 (Box 109, Folder 24)
  - The Council of Ivy Group Presidents, 1999-2001 (Box 109, Folder 25-31)
  - Collegiate Licensing/Sweatshops, 2000-2001 (Box 109, Folder 32-34)
  - Knight Foundation, 1986, 1999-2001 (Box 109, Folder 35)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 2000-2001 (Box 109, Folder 36-37)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 2001 (Box 109, Folder 38)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant, 2000-2001 (Box 109, Folder 39)
  - National Academies, 2000-2001, 2005-2006 (Box 109, Folder 40)
  - President's Office, 2000-2001 (Box 109, Folder 41-42)
  - Overseas Development Council, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Overseas Development Council, 1998-1999 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Overseas Development Council, 1999-2000 (Box 110, Folder 3-4)
  - (URA) Universities Research Association, 2000-2001 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Corporations- Miscellaneous, 2000-2001 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Corporate Codes of Conduct, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Business, Science, and the Universities, Bok, Kennedy CCSPU, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Corning Glass, 2000-2001 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Corning/Cornell Partnership, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - General Electric, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - General Motors, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Hewlett Packard, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - IBM, 2000-2001 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Procter and Gamble, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Shell Oil, 2000-2001 (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Fellowships/Scholarships, 2000-2001 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Hardis Scholarship Winner, 1999 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - Weiss Fellowship, 2000-2001 (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - List of Recipients of Weiss Fellowships, 1993-1998 (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - Prizes and Awards, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 22-23)
  - Prizes and Awards, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 24)
  - Case PROF of Year, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 25)
  - Case PROF of Year, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 26)
  - Case PROF of Year, 1995-1996 (Box 110, Folder 27)
  - Case PROF of Year, 1996-1997 (Box 110, Folder 28)
  - Case PROF of Year, 1995-1996 (Box 110, Folder 29-30)
  - Frank H.T. Rhodes Exemplary Service Award, 1994-1995 (Box 110, Folder 31)
  - Nomination of Students and Faculty for Special Awards, 1984-1985 (Box 110, Folder 32)
  - David Starr Jordan Prize, 1987, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 33)
  - David Starr Jordan Prize, 1984-1986 (Box 110, Folder 34-35)
  - Foundations, 2001-2002 (Box 110, Folder 36)
  - Foundations, 2000-2001 (Box 110, Folder 37-40)
  - Corporation and Foundation Presentation, 1978 (Box 110, Folder 41)
  - Corporation Foundation: Supplement II Presentation (Box 110, Folder 42)
  - Corporation Foundation Presentation Basic (Box 110, Folder 43)
  - Corporation Foundation I Supplement, 1978 (Box 110, Folder 44)
  - World Center, 1982, 1988, 1993-1994 (Box 110, Folder 45)
  - World Center, 1986-1988 (Box 110, Folder 46-50)
  - World Center, 1987-1989 (Box 110, Folder 51)
  - (APS) Atlantic Philanthropic Service Corp., 2001 (Box 110, Folder 52)
  - (APS) Atlantic Philanthropic Service Meeting, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 53)
  - (APS) Atlantic Philanthropic Service Corp., 2000-2001 (Box 110, Folder 54-58)
  - (APS) Atlantic Philanthropic Service Transition Article, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 59)
  - (APS) Atlantic Philanthropic Service Commitment Letters- Not Received, 1996-1998 (Box 110, Folder 60)
  - The Ford Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - The Guggenheim Foundation, 2001 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - The Hewlett Foundation (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - The Kellogg Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - The Kresge Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - The Luce Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - The Mellon Foundation (Avalon Foundation), 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - The National Science Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - The Park Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - The Pew Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - The Rockefeller Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - The Sloan Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - The Teagle Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - The Whitaker Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - The Whitaker Proposal, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - The Whitaker Proposal, 1999-2000 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - Accreditation Reviews, March 11, 1996 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Accreditation Reviews, 1991-1992, 1995-1996, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - Colleges- Statutory General, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - Y2K/Smart N.Y., 1999 (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - Susan A. Henry, 2001 (Box 111, Folder 22-24)
  - CALS #2, 1999-2000 (Box 111, Folder 25-28)
  - Institute for Biotech and Life Science Tech. (BLIST), 2000 (Box 111, Folder 29)
  - Department of Molecular Biology and Genetics (MBG), 2000 (Box 111, Folder 30)
  - Carlos Castillo-Chavez (Box 111, Folder 31)
  - Christy, Ralph, 2000 (Box 111, Folder 32)
  - Lauren Doliner, 2001 (Box 111, Folder 33)
  - Hagen, James, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 34)
  - Pamela Stepp, 2000 (Box 111, Folder 35)
  - Biometrics Reorganization to Departments of Biostatistics and Computational Biology (CALS), 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 36)
  - Punta Cana, 1998-1999, 2001 (Box 111, Folder 37)
  - Plant Pathology Herbarium, 2001 (Box 111, Folder 38)
  - Cornell University- China Initiative (NRS), 1999 (Box 111, Folder 39)
  - Baranowski, 1996, 1998 (Box 111, Folder 40)
  - Biddy, Martin, 1999-2001 (Box 111, Folder 41)
  - Biddy, Martin, 2001 (Box 111, Folder 42)
  - Biddy, Martin, 2001 (Box 111, Folder 43)
  - AG- Cornell International Institute for Food, Agriculture and Development (CIIFAD), 1999-2001 (Box 111, Folder 44)
  - AG- CIIFAD, 2000-2001 (Box 111, Folder 45)
  - CIIFAD- Governing Board (Box 111, Folder 46)
  - CIIFAD- External Review and History (Box 111, Folder 47)
  - Cooperative Extension, 1994-1998, 2000-2001 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Boyce Thompson Institute, 2000-2001 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Sea Grant Institute, 1997, 2000 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Architecture, 1998, 2000-2001 (Box 112, Folder 4-5)
  - Architecture-Accreditation, 1998-1999 (Box 112, Folder 6-7)
  - Stein Institute for Landscape and Urban Studies, 1998 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Milstein, Howard, 1998 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2001, 2003 (Box 112, Folder 10-15)
  - To Hunter, from Earl, November 21, 1997 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Department Visual Studies (A and S), 1998 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Lincoln Hall Donors (A and S), 1998 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Hull Publication Fund, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Walter McCrane (Chemistry) (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2000 (Box 112, Folder 21-22)
  - Arts and Sciences Curriculum Report, 2000 (Box 112, Folder 23)
  - Institute for the study of Social Inequality (ISSI) (David Grusky), 1999-2000 (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Poverty, Inequality, and Development Initiative (PID), 2000 (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Arts and Sciences Committee on Curriculum (Box 112, Folder 26)
  - Classics, 2000-2001 (Box 112, Folder 27)
  - Performing Arts Facility, 2000 (Box 112, Folder 28)
  - Society for the Humanities, 2000 (Box 112, Folder 29)
  - Criticism/Theory, 1997-1998 (Box 112, Folder 30)
  - Humanities Report, 1998 (Box 112, Folder 31)
  - Humanities Task Force, 1998 (Box 112, Folder 32)
  - College of Engineering, 2001 (Box 112, Folder 33-36)
  - Office of the President/Women in the Chemical Workforce, 2001 (Box 112, Folder 37)
  - Provost/President's Office, 2001 (Box 112, Folder 38)
  - College of Engineering, 2000-2001 (Box 112, Folder 39-40)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 1999-2001 (Box 112, Folder 41)
  - Earth and Atmospheric Sciences, 1998-2001 (Box 112, Folder 42)
  - Geological Sciences, 1998 (Box 112, Folder 43)
  - Bioengineering, 1999-2000 (Box 112, Folder 44)
  - Whitaker Proposal, 2000-2001 (Box 112, Folder 45)
  - Barazangi, Muawia (Box 112, Folder 46)
  - Engineering- Dean Review (OMR folder), 1998 (Box 112, Folder 47)
  - Garza Paper on Computer Science, 2000 (Box 112, Folder 48)
  - Computing and Information Sciences Task Force Report, 1999 (Box 112, Folder 49)
  - Computer Science Est. 1965, 1986, 1997 (Box 112, Folder 50)
  - Graduate School, 2000-2001 (Box 113, Folder 1-2)
  - Graduate Tuition Policy (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Hotel School, 2001 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Hotel School, 2000 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Statler Club, 1999-2000 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Memo of Understanding Hotel School and Chinese University of Hong Kong, 1998 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Dean Search Hotel, 2000 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - CU- China Exchange, 2000-2001 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - CU- China Scholars Program, 2000 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Meeting with Chuck Feeney/ Dr. Edw. Walsh in Shannon, Ireland Re: Limerick Agreement, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Johnson Art Museum, 2000-2001 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University Press, 2000-2001 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Human Ecology, 2000-2001 (Box 113, Folder 14-15)
  - Human Ecology, 1999-2000 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - CU- Ithaca Flats Community Outreach Partnership Center (COPC) (P. Pollack), 1999 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Center for Policy Research (Lewin Group), 2000 (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - Brumberg, Joan, 2001 (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - Kutty, Nandinee, 1998-2000 (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - Parrot, Andrea, 2000 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - CIPA- Institute of Public Affairs, 2000-2001 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Nutrition, 2000-2001 (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - Industrial and Labor Relations, 2000-2001 (Box 113, Folder 24)
  - Johnson Graduate School of Management, 1999-2001 (Box 113, Folder 25-26)
  - Venture Fund and "Virtual Incubator", 2000 (Box 113, Folder 27)
  - Cayuga MBA Fund, 1998 (Box 113, Folder 28)
  - College of Insurance, 2000 (Box 113, Folder 29-30)
  - Law School, 2000-2001 (Box 113, Folder 31)
  - Veterinary Medicine, 2001, 2006 (Box 113, Folder 32-33)
  - Veterinary Medicine, 2000 (Box 113, Folder 35-37)
  - Moon, Paula (Tenure), 1999 (Box 113, Folder 38)
  - Medical College- Correspondence, 2006 (Box 113, Folder 39)
  - Cornell University Medical College- Accreditation Review, 1995-1996 (Box 113, Folder 40)
  - Cornell University Medical College- Dean's Letters, 2000-2001 (Box 113, Folder 41)
  - Cornell University Medical College- Dean's Search, 1999 (Box 113, Folder 42)
  - Cornell University Medical College- Code of Conduct (Box 113, Folder 43)
  - Joan and Sanford I. Weill Medical College, 1999-2001 (Box 113, Folder 44-45)
  - Joan and Sanford I. Weill Medical College, 1998-2000 (Box 113, Folder 46)
  - Search- Chair-Pediatrics, 2001 (Box 113, Folder 47)
  - Cornell Center for Complementary and Integrate Medicine Proposal, 1999 (Box 113, Folder 48)
  - Pardes, New York Hospital, 1999 (Box 113, Folder 49)
  - Search- Cell Biology Chair, 2000 (Box 113, Folder 50)
  - GenVAC Proposal, 1998 (Box 113, Folder 51)
  - STARR FND. Grant to CUMC, 2000 (Box 113, Folder 52)
  - Joint LAY Leadership Oversight Group, 1998 (Box 113, Folder 53)
  - Cornell/Harvard/Yale Consortium (chess), 1996-1997 (Box 113, Folder 54)
  - CUMC- (Nathan and Lloyd Old), 1998 (Box 113, Folder 55)
  - Boards and Membership Lists, 1996-1997 (Box 113, Folder 56)
  - CUMC: Endowment/Named Programs, 1997 (Box 113, Folder 57)
  - Affiliation Agreement inc. Hospital for Special Surgery, 1997 (Box 113, Folder 58)
  - QATAR Initiative (CUMC), 2001 (Box 114, Folder 1-4)
  - Society of the New York Hospital and Cornell University Agreement, 1927 (Box 114, Folder 4A)
  - NY Hospital and Presbyterian Hospital Merger, 1995-1997 (Box 114, Folder 5-10)
  - NYH/CU Joint Agreements COL/Presbyterian NYH/CUMC Operating Rules, 1977, 1995-1997 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - NYH/CUMC Reorganization, 1995-1996 (Box 114, Folder 11A)
  - Cornell University Medical College-Long Range Planning, 1995, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University Medical College-Strategic Plan, 1995, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 13-14)
  - Tri-Institutional Research Program, 2000-2001 (Box 114, Folder 15-17)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center Annual Report, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Tri-Institutional Program, 2000-2001 (Box 114, Folder 19-20)
  - Bioinformatics, July, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - Tri-Institutional Computational Biology Center, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - Tri-Institutional Program, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 24-25)
  - Tri-Institutional Proposal, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - Tri-Institutional Cooperative Venture, 1998-2000 (Box 114, Folder 27-31)
  - Conjoint Board Minutes, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 32)
  - Columbia- Cornell Care, LLC-Gen., 2000-2001 (Box 114, Folder 33)